NYSUT Additional Records 5720
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Welfare Trust, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Welfare Trust, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Westchester County Public School System Survey on Fringe Benefits, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Work Stoppages (NYSUT), 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 31)